Guide to the Robert Stanley Breed papers, [ca. 1901-1943]
Breed, Robert Stanley papers, [ca. 1901-1943]
- Geneva Experimental Station correspondence
  - Dairy and Food Products (Minutes of Meeting, etc.) (Box 16)
  - Media and Agar. (Box 16)
  - Direct Microscopic Examination (Box 16)
  - Dilution Bottles (Box 16)
  - List of Errata (Box 16)
  - Revised Grade A. Sampling Plan (Box 16)
  - History of Standard Methods (Box 16)
  - Ice Cream (Box 16)
  - Bacteriological Incubators (Box 16)
  - Milk Tests and Literature References (Box 16)
  - Minutes of Standard Methods Meeting (Box 16)
  - Rinsing Milk Bottles and Cans (Box 16)
  - 32 Standard Methods Committee, Milk Report, Fourth edition, mss. (Box 16)
- Robert S. Breed papers
  - W.A. Stocking, 1919 (Box 17)
  - Coordinating Committee, 1945-1947 (Box 17)
  - APHA Lab Section, 1933-1938 (Box 17)
  - Society of American Bacteriology, 1944-1948 (Box 17)
  - Reports and Minutes of Standards Committee, 1921-1932 (Box 17)
  - Correspondence, 1915-1948 (Box 17)
  - Abstracts of the correspodnence of selected correspondents (typescript and mimeo) (Box 18)
  - 32 Standard Methods of Milk Analysis, 1949-1951 (Box 18)
  - Bergey Manual and Correspondence, reprints, etc., 1938, 1948-1949 (Box 18)
  - Cheese work notebook, A.W.B., 1906-1909 (Box 18)
  - Volume of newspaper clippings, 1906-1908 (Box 18)
  - Printed material, 1901-1923 (Box 18)